

#### **SKILLS**

- Bootstrap, JQuery, Javascript, CSS and HTML
- Wordpress with Elementor
- Data Entry
- Customer Service
- Social Media Manager
- ConnectWise Email Marketing

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering**

University of Southern Mindanao | March 2009

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Virtual Assistant with a demonstrated history of working in the outsourcing/offshoring industry and also in web development industry for more than 4 years by developing websites using Bootstrap, Javascript, CSS, HTML and jQuery and mostly front-end development. I'm using Wordpress as CMS and Elementor as web page builder.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

## **Virtual Assistant**

#### Upwork | July 2015 - present

Account Executive in Sales Department

- Submitting quotes to customers
- Process purchase orders
- Tracking orders

# Customer Service Representative

# Transcom Iloilo | February 2015 - May 2015

- Inbound calls for billing inquiries from customers
- Selling Cable, Internet and Phone Services

## Web Developer

# Sell2Any B.V. | June 2014 - November 2014

· Convert PSD web design into HTML file using bootstrap

# Web Developer

## HPO Phil., Inc. | October 2013 - March 2014

• Helped Team developed Funnel Websites using WordPress

# **Software Programmer**

#### Geodata Solutions Inc. | July 2009 - September 2013

Helped Team developed the Hospital Information System

- Design the graphical user interface of every module
- Writing backend codes
- Tests the system for quality assurance.

# **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Email: markozpaez1525@gmail.com

Website: https://markozpaez.netlify.app

**Contact:** +63928-127-4145 **Address:** Jaro, Iloilo City 5000